I'm tired of being
what you want me to be
Feeling so faithless,
lost under the surface
I don't know what you're
expecting of me
Put under the pressure,
of walking in your shoes
(Caught in the undertow,
just caught in the undertow)
Every step that I take is
another mistake to you...
(Caught in the undertow,
just caught in the undertow)
I've become so numb,
I can't feel you there
Become so tired,
so much more aware
I'm becoming this,
all I want to do
Is be more like me
and be less like you
Can't you see that
you're smothering me?
Holding too tightly,
afraid to lose control
'Cause everything
that you thought I would be
Has fallen apart,
right in front of you
(Caught in the undertow,
just caught in the undertow)
Every step that I take
is another mistake to you
(Caught in the undertow,
just caught in the undertow)
An' every second I waste
is more than I can take...
I've become so numb,
I can't feel you there
Become so tired,
so much more aware
I'm becoming this,
all I want to do
Is be more like me
and be less like you
And I know
I may end up failing too
But I know You were just like me,
with someone disappointed in you...
I've become so numb,
I can't feel you there
Become so tired,
so much more aware
I'm becoming this,
all I want to do
Is be more like me
and be less like you
I've become so numb,
I can't feel you there
(I'm tired of being
what you want me to be)
I've become so numb,
I can't feel you there
(I'm tired of being
what you want me to be)