(It starts with)
One thing... I dont know why
It doesnt even matter how hard you try
Keep that in mind I designed
this rhyme, To explain in due time
(All I know) Time is a valuable thing
Watch it fly by as the pendulum swings
Watch it count down to the end
of the day, The clock ticks life away
(Its so unreal) Didnt look out below
Watch the time go right out the window
Trying to hold on but didnt even know
Wasted it all just to
(Watch you go) I kept everything
inside and even though I tried,
it all fell apart
What it meant to me, will eventually,
be a memory, of a time when
(I tried so hard and got so far)
But in the end
It doesn't even matter
I had to fall to lose it all
But in the end
It doesn't even matter
One thing I dont know why
It doesnt even matter how hard you try
Keep that in mind I designed this rhyme
To remind myself how (I tried so hard...)
In spite of the way you were mocking me
Acting like I was part of your property
Remembering all the times you fought with me
Im surprised (it got so far...)
Things arent the way they were before
You wouldnt even recognize me anymore
Not that you knew me back then
But it all comes back to me
(In the end...)You kept everything inside
And even though I tried it all fell apart
What it meant to me, will eventually,
be a memory, of a time when
(I tried so hard and got so far)
But in the end
It doesnt even matter
I had to fall to lose it all
But in the end
It doesnt even matter...
I've put my trust in you
Pushed as far as I can go
For all this, Theres only
one thing you should know...
I've put my trust in you
Pushed as far as I can go
For all this, Theres only one thing
you should know...
I tried so hard
And got so far
But in the end
It doesnt even matter
I had to fall to lose it all
But in the end
It doesnt even matter...